Moore, Frank C.; Papers apap223
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Conferences, Commissions and Committees, 1947-1971; 8
  - Committee on Constitutional Tax and Debt Limitations and City-School Fiscal Relations (CTDL-CSFR), 1947-1953; 8.1; 3 cubic ft.
    - City - School Fiscal Relations - Background Material on Fiscal Independence (Binder), [1951?]; 2 folders (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 14-15)
    - City & Village Tax Limits; New York City, 1948-1949; binder (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 16)
    - Committee on CTDL - CSFR - First Report, 1948 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 17)
    - Committee on CTDL - CSFR - Second Report, 1949 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 18)
    - Committee on CTDL - CSFR - School Buildings Report (Third Report), 1950 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 19)
    - Committee on CTDL - CSFR - Constitutional Debt Limitation Amendment (Fourth Report), 1951 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 20)
    - Committee on CTDL - CSFR - Memorandum of Major Accomplishments, 1953 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 21)
    - Constitutional Tax & Debt Limitations, 1947-1948; 3 folders (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 22-24)
    - Constitutional Tax & Debt Limitations, 1948-1949; binder (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 25)
    - Copies of Proposal - Tax Limit, 1948 (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 26)
    - Counties & Reports, 1948-1949; 2 folders (Box 31 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 27-28)
    - Debt, 1947-1948; binder (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 1)
    - Debt, 1948-1949; 2 folders (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 2-3)
    - Debt (Binder 1 of 3), 1949-1950 (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 4)
    - Debt (Binder 2 of 3), 1949-1950; 2 folders (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 5-6)
    - Debt (Binder 3 of 3), 1949-1950 (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 7)
    - Debt, 1950-1951; 2 folders (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 8-9)
    - Debt Charts, 1949-1950; binder (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 10)
    - Desk Folder, 1953 (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 11)
    - Equalization Rates / Federal Aid, 1948-1949; 2 folders (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 12-13)
    - Fiscal Independence, 1951-1953 (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 14)
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 15)
    - General Description of Tax Limit Amendment, Undated (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 16)
    - The Geographical Relationship Between the Cities and City School Districts in New York State (Report), 1948; 2 folders (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 17-18)
    - Meeting, 10/8/1951 (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 19)
    - Meeting, 11/7/1951 (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 20)
    - Meeting, 12/20-21/1951 (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 21)
    - Meeting, 12/20-21/1951 (Box 32 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 22)
    - Meeting, 1/7/1952 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 1/7/1952 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 2)
    - Meeting, 1/16/1952 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 3)
    - Meeting, 1/20/1952 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 4)
      (Hotel Roosevelt, New York City - Cancelled).
    - Meeting, 1/22-23/1952 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 1/22-23/1952 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 6)
    - Meeting ("Fiscal Independence"), 2/12/1952 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 3/17/1952 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 8)
    - Meeting ("Big 5" Hearing), 1/14/1953; 2 folders (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 9-10)
    - Meeting, 1/29/1953 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 11)
      (Rough Copies of Material).
    - Meeting, 1/29/1953; 2/20/1953 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 12)
    - Meeting (Final Meeting), 10/9/1953 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 13)
    - Memorandum of Major Accomplishments, 1953 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 14)
    - Municipal Affairs (Binder 1), 1947-1948; 2 binders (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 15-16)
    - New York City (Binder 1), 1949-1950; 2 binders (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 17-18)
    - New York City, 1952-1953 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 19)
    - Notes, 1951 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 20)
    - Notes for Next Meeting, 1948-1949 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 21)
    - Origins of Tax Limits, 1948 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 22)
    - Personnel, 1948-1950 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 23)
    - Publicity, 1949-1952 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 24)
    - Real Estate Tax Memoranda, 1952-1953 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 25)
    - School Districts, 1948 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 26)
    - Tax Limits - All 48 States (Project no. 10), 1947-1948 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 27)
    - Tax Limits - Counties, 1948-1950 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 28)
    - Tax Limits - Evasions, Undated (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 29)
    - Tax Limits - Schools, 1949 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 30)
    - Tax Limits - Villages, 1947 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 31)
    - Tax Trends, 1948 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 32)
    - Travel Expenses, Vouchers, etc., 1947-1953 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 33)
    - Villages, 1948 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 34)
    - Wealth, 1947-1950 (Box 33 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 35)
  - State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1947-1971; 8.2; 1.5 cubic ft.
    This series contains the records of the State Board of Equalization and Assessment, on which Moore served for over two decades. The materials in this series are primarily organized chronologically; yearly folders document the activities of the Board from year to year. However, the series also includes several subject files, such as several binders of material on the Assessment Advisory Committee and a 1963 report on "Principles and Procedures Used in Establishing State Equalization Rates", which are organized alphabetically.
    - Assessment Advisory Committee, Items 31-34 (Binder), 1958 (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 1)
    - Assessment Advisory Committee, Item 35 (Binder), 1958 (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 2)
    - Assessment Advisory Committee, Item 36 (Binder), 1958 (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 3)
    - Assessment Advisory Committee, Items 37-39 (Binder), 1958 (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 4)
    - Assessment Advisory Committee Meetings, 1956-1959; 2 folders (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 5-6)
    - Organization Charts, 1959-1965 (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 7)
    - Principles and Procedures Used in Establishing State Equalization Rates, 1963 (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 8)
    - Program Structure Outline, 1968; binder (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 9)
    - Revised Equalization Rates, 1954; binder (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 10)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1947-1963 (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 11)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment (Binder 1), 1949; 2 binders (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 12-13)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1952-1953? (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 14)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment (Binder 1), 1953; 2 folders (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 15-16)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment (Binder 2), 1953 (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 17)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment (Binder 3), 1953; 3 folders (Box 34 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 18-20)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment (Binder 4), 1953; 2 folders (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 1-2)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1953-1954 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 3)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1964 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 4)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1965; 3 folders (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 5-7)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1966 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 8)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1967 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 9)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1968-1969 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 10)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1969-1971 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 11)
    - State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1953-1954; Oversized (Box 55 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 2)
  - White House Conference on Education, 1954-1957; 8.3; 2.5 cubic ft.
    This series contains records related to the 1955 White House Conference on Education at which Moore served as Chairman of the Finance Committee. Records include the minutes of preparatory meetings, correspondence, an extensive file of research material documenting school financing practices throughout the United States, and drafts of reports. The original filing scheme of this series, in which files are arranged alphabetically under several headings (primarily "Finance Subcommittee", "General", and "Publications"), has been maintained in the present arrangement.
    - Finance Subcommittee - Applications to Foundations, 1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 12)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Biographies, 1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 13)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Committee of Four (Elder/Freeman/Hubbard/Miles), 1956; Undated (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 14)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 15)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Correspondence Subcommittee Members, 1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 16)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Freeman, Roger, 1955-1956; 2 folders (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 17-18)
    - Finance Subcommittee - General, 1954-1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 19)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Johns, Dr. Lyell, 1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 20)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Material for Conference Participants - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 21)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Meetings, 1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 22)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Members, List of, 1954-1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 23)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Mills, Dr. Robert, 1955-1957 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 24)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Morphet, Edgar L., 1955-1956 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 25)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Needs By States, U.S. Office of Education, 1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 26)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Notes for Discussion, 1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 27)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Reports - Subcommittee, 1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 28)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Proposed Program, 1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 29)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Report Drafts (Folder 1 of 2), 1955 (Box 35 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 30)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Report Drafts (Folder 2 of 2), 1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 1)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Report of Finance Subcommittee (Marked Copy), 1955-1956 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 2)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Reports - Chairman, 1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 3)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Tentative Report, 1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 4)
    - Finance Subcommittee - Worksheets, 1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 5)
    - General - Act of Congress and President's Message, 1955-1956 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 6)
    - General - Applications for Funds by States, 1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 7)
    - General - Appointment to Conference, 1954 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 8)
    - General - Background Data, 1954 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 9)
    - General - Background Material, 11/28/1955-12/1/1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 10)
    - General - Better Schools Conference Kit, 1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 11)
    - General - Brownell, Dr. Samuel M. (U.S. Commissioner of Education), 1953-1954 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 12)
    - General - Conference, 11/28/1955-12/01/1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 13)
    - General - Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 14)
    - General - Dissenting Opinions, 1955-1956 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 15)
    - General - Drafts and Correspondence, 1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 16)
    - General - Field Representatives, 1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 17)
    - General - Information Packet, [1955?] (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 18)
    - General - McElroy, Neil, 1955-1956 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 19)
    - General - Members, list of, 1954 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 20)
    - General - Notes for Discussion, 1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 21)
    - General - Pace, Clint, 1955-1956 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 22)
    - General - President's Committee - First Meeting - Agenda, 12/2/1954 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 23)
    - General - President's Committee - Second Meeting - Agenda, 1/18/1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 24)
    - General - President's Committee - Second Meeting - Informational Material, 1/18/1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 25)
    - General - President's Committee - Third Meeting - Agenda, 3/21/1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 26)
    - General - President's Committee - Fourth Meeting - Agenda, 5/11/1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 27)
    - General - President's Committee - Fifth Meeting - Agenda, 7/8/1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 28)
    - General - Procedures - Travel, etc., 1956; Undated (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 29)
    - General - Prospectus, 1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 30)
    - General - Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 31)
    - General - Report to the President, 1956 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 32)
    - General - Research Material (Folder 1 of 9), 1954-1955 (Box 36 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 33)
    - General - Research Material (Folders 2-9 of 9), 1954-1955; 8 folders (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 1-8)
    - General - School Districts by State, 1955 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 9)
    - General - Speeches, 1955 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 10)
    - General - Speech, FCM to Main Committee, 11/30/1955 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 1955 September 01-1955 September 02 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 12)
    - Meeting, 1955 October 06 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 13)
    - Meeting, 1956 January 16-1956 January 17 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 14)
    - Publications - Association for Childhood Education International, 1955 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 15)
    - Publications -Better Schools, 1955-1956 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 16)
    - Publications - General, 1955 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 17)
    - Publications -Life Magazine, "Why Teacher Stays Poor", 1955 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 18)
    - Publications - Newsletter, 1955 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 19)
    - State Conferences and Committees - New York State Committee, 1955 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 20)
    - State Conferences and Committees - State Conferences, 1954-1955 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 21)
    - Subcommittees - Organization, 1955 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 22)
    - Subcommittees - Workbook for Educational Conferences, 1955 (Box 37 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 23)
  - Commission on State - Local Fiscal Relations, 1963-1965; 8.4; 0.5 cubic ft.
    This series contains the records of the Commission on State-Local Fiscal Relations. It is organized chronologically except for a pair of subject files containing a membership list and a draft of the Commission's final report.
    - Commission on State - Local Fiscal Relations, 1963; 3 folders (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 1-3)
    - Commission on State - Local Fiscal Relations, 1964; 2 folders (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 4-5)
    - Commission on State - Local Fiscal Relations, 1965; 4 folders (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 6-9)
    - Final Report (Draft), 1965 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 10)
    - Membership, 1963 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Conferences, Commissions and Committees, 1945-1963; 8.5; 2 cubic ft.
    This series contains the records of conferences, commissions and committees whose extant records in this collection are less than .5 cubic feet. The subseries is organized alphabetically by committee name. It includes records from the American Council to Improve Our Neighborhoods (A.C.T.I.O.N.), the Public Works Planning Committee, the New York State Advisory Committee on Teachers' Salaries, the Commission on Municipal Revenues and Reduction of Real Estate Taxes, the New York State Temporary Commission on School Buildings, the National Conference on Metropolitan Problems, and the Committee on Special Local Non-Property Taxes. Committees are typically represented by reports, internal notes and memoranda, and informational binders.
    - American Council to Improve Our Neighborhoods (A.C.T.I.O.N.) - Financial Statements, 1956 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 12)
    - American Council to Improve Our Neighborhoods (A.C.T.I.O.N.) - Organization Chart, 1956 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 13)
    - American Council to Improve Our Neighborhoods (A.C.T.I.O.N.) - Reports - Miscellaneous, 1954-1960 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 14)
    - American Council to Improve Our Neighborhoods (A.C.T.I.O.N.) - Research Program: Impediments in the Housing Market, 1956-1959 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 15)
    - American Council to Improve Our Neighborhoods (A.C.T.I.O.N.) - Speeches, 1956-1958 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 16)
    - American Council to Improve Our Neighborhoods (A.C.T.I.O.N.) - Urban Renewal, 1957-1958 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 17)
    - Public Works Planning Committee - Bragdon, General J.S., 1956-1957 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 18)
    - Public Works Planning Committee - General, 1956; 3 folders (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 19-21)
    - Public Works Planning Committee - Meeting, 06/1956 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 22)
    - Public Works Planning Committee - Members and Standing Committee, 1956 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 23)
    - Public Works Planning Committee - Memoranda, 1956-1957 (Box 38 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 24)
    - Public Works Planning Committee - State - Local Advisory Committee on Public Works Planning, 1956 (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 1)
    - Committee and Commission Membership Lists, 1963 (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 2)
    - Committee and Commission Membership Lists, Undated (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 3)
    - New York State Advisory Committee on Teachers' Salaries - Advisory Committee on Teachers' Salaries (Binder), 1951; 2 folders (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 4-5)
    - New York State Advisory Committee on Teachers' Salaries - Notebook, 1950-1951 (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 6)
    - New York State Advisory Committee on Teachers' Salaries - Teachers' Salary Study (Binder 1), 1951; 2 folders (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 7-8)
    - New York State Advisory Committee on Teachers' Salaries - Teachers' Salary Study (Binder 2), 1951; 2 folders (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 9-10)
    - New York State Advisory Committee on Teachers' Salaries - Teachers' Salary Study (Binder 3), 1951; 2 folders (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 11-12)
    - New York State Advisory Committee on Teachers' Salaries - Teachers' Salary Study (Binder 4), 1951 (Box 39 (8-Conferences, Commissions and Committees), Folder 13)